Uneku Ogbaje

Frontend Developer

Lagos, Nigeria (+234) 8140086240 unekuogbaje@gmail.com

PROFILE

I'm a Frontend Developer with three years of hands-on programming experience. I have spent the last couple of years working on applications for the web. Emphasizing architecture, scalability, design, user interface, and testing. I have worked successfully with teams, and start-ups to visually transform their ideas and create excellent products that meet organizational goals and increase user conversion.

I seek positions that offer challenges, career prospects, and development, achieving set targets and organizational objectives.

EXPERIENCE

BroadPage Technologies, Lagos — Frontend Developer

Jun. 2022 - Date

- Develop new user-facing features
- Determine the structure of web pages
- Optimize web pages for maximum efficiency
- Work closely with the design team

Afriex -, Lagos — Frontend Developer

Nov. 2020 - Mar. 2021

- Hands-on frontend development based on wireframes & visual designs.
- Release of content that works across different browsers and devices.

SOME OF MY PROJECTS

Quote-Generator - A Javascript project by Uneku

This is a web app that generates random quotes from an API. Quotes can also be tweeted directly from the app.

Check it out!

Rainbow - A React project by Uneku

This is a simple react web app created with create-react-app and styled with tailwind CSS.

Have a look!

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF JOS - 2011-2016

B.Ed Geography

Meta - 2022

Frontend Developer Certification

Google - 2022

Google UX Design Certification

ACHIEVEMENTS

During the pandemic of 2020, I began my transition into the tech space and have since mastered a number of frontend skills and languages

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

HTMI.

CSS, Tailwind CSS & SCSS

JavaScript

React.JS (Native)

Next.JS

LANGUAGES

English & Hausa

Find me on <u>GitHub</u> and <u>Twitter</u>.